<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en"><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.6.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" /><updated>2021-03-26T08:28:06+00:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">News</title><subtitle>The Portal to the New, Open Internet.</subtitle><entry xml:lang="en"><title type="html">Mask Network x Cent | Buy the Tweet you just saw on Twitter</title><link href="/2021/03/26/mask-network-x-cent-buy-the-tweet-you-just-saw-on-twitter" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mask Network x Cent | Buy the Tweet you just saw on Twitter" /><published>2021-03-26T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-03-26T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2021/03/26/mask-network-x-cent-buy-the-tweet-you-just-saw-on-twitter</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/03/26/mask-network-x-cent-buy-the-tweet-you-just-saw-on-twitter">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/1-49.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mask Network is collaborating with Cent through a joint bounty to add NFTs directly to Twitter: bid and trade on tweets directly within Twitter to support those who tweet!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bounty link:&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/DimensionDev/Maskbook/issues/2599&quot;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://gitcoin.co/issue/DimensionDev/Maskbook/2599&quot; title=&quot;https://gitcoin.co/issue/DimensionDev/Maskbook/2599&quot;&gt;https://gitcoin.co/issue/DimensionDev/Maskbook/2599&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With support from Valuables, the tweet minting platform made by Cent, Mask Network aims to enable users to trade tweets as NFTs directly on Twitter, and in the near future, allows an instant look into the tweet’s bidding history. When a user feels a connection to a particular tweet, or wants to support the person/organization that created the tweet, they can now bid on an NFT of that tweet, directly within Twitter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jack Dorsey, the co-founder and CEO of Twitter, had listed his very first tweet for sale as an NFT on Valuables. The sale ended on March 21st, and the tweet was sold for over $2.9 million USD. All profits were converted into Bitcoin and donated to the charity GiveDirectly’s Africa response.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/2-47.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What does it mean to “own” a tweet?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The tweet itself will continue to live on Twitter. What users purchased is a digital certificate of the tweet, unique and signed by the creator using cryptography. Apart from the digital signature from the creator’s crypto wallet address, the digital certificate includes metadata of the original tweet: who posted it, when it was posted, the contents of the tweet, and more. All metadata lives on the Matic blockchain. Users could do whatever they want with the tweet they own: resell them on Valuables or display them in your online gallery.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Content creators on Twitter will be able to trade tweets using the Mask Network extension, and see value in the tweets they create. Everything takes place on Twitter directly, so there’s no need to navigate out of the native twitter experience.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mask Network did some experiments within the NFT field: During last year’s US election, Mask Network posted 589 “US Election Special Edition NFTs” on its official Twitter account. We also embedded a “Collectibles” feature into the “Dashboard,” where users could check the art pieces they own as NFTs directly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/110528663503787843.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the near future, Mask Network will carry on developing new features for NFTs, making it easier to create, collect, and trade NFTs on centralized platforms (e.g. Twitter, Facebook, Instagram…). Now that concepts such as NFTs and Web 3.0 are becoming better known, Mask Network hopes to accelerate adoption and welcome more users to the benefits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/654594827388748385.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We at Mask Network believe NFTs represent more than tweets or digital art. In the future, multi-category NFTs will form a new on-chain e-commerce world; the products and applications we see now are only the tip of the iceberg. Mask Network shares a similar vision with Cent, which is to be the platform for creators to showcase their work, to bring context to NFTs in many forms, and to let users reclaim the ownership of their digital identities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Cent / Valuables&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cent is a platform powered by digital identity. Cent provides tools for those who create, curate, and collaborate for a living, replacing the traditional info feed with an immersive gallery. Those who support the gallery form a community, generate income for creators. Content creators could display their own gallery to the community, or license their work to another gallery and distribute within the community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cent believes that digital identity carries three principles: yours, forever, and interoperable. All activities a user generated (text, picture, videos, interactions…) solely belong to the user and collaborators. Users should hold control with where content appears, how personal data are used, and most importantly, how it is monetized. Every record of ownership is kept in an encrypted digital storage that is maintained on a public network, users will have access at all times. Their digital identity doesn’t depend on any single platform. Users are free to create identity on any of the existing (and upcoming) networks, and transfer freely between them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Mask Network&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mask Network is the core product of Dimension, which is positioned to become the bridge that connects internet users from Web 2.0 to Web 3.0. The foundational technology of Mask Network is a peer to peer encrypted messaging application, with new functions continuously being created around this foundation. We at Mask Network are strong believers in the ownership economy. People should own what they produce, people should own their data, their attention and the virtual space they choose to contribute to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mask Network integrates decentralized social messaging, borderless payment network, and decentralized file storage and sharing to provide a safe and convenient portal for users to jump right into the continent of decentralized finance and then the new world of Web 3.0.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/%7B%7B%20site.baseurl_root%20%7D%7D/uploads/1-49.png" /></entry><entry xml:lang="en"><title type="html">$MASK Token Unlock Details (March 2021)</title><link href="/2021/03/24/mask-token-unlock-details-march-2021" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="$MASK Token Unlock Details (March 2021)" /><published>2021-03-24T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-03-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2021/03/24/mask-token-unlock-details-march-2021</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/03/24/mask-token-unlock-details-march-2021">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/771038253706819007.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It has been nearly a month since the official launch of the $MASK token, we appreciate your active participation in our ITO and LBP. After some careful consideration, we are ready to release the allocation of $MASK token and the progress of unlocking at each stage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Please referto:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://news.mask.io/2021/02/11/introducing-the-mask-token&quot; title=&quot;https://news.mask.io/2021/02/11/introducing-the-mask-token&quot;&gt;https://news.mask.io/2021/02/11/introducing-the-mask-token&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See the table below for $MASK token first unlock (March 29th, 2021) details:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/654770200978803623.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A total of 10,913,333 $MASK, 10.91% of the total supply will be circulating after the first month unlock (March, 2021) . 9% has been circulating for the first month. 1.91% will be released this time.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Of the 1.91% released this time, 1.1% comes from the foundation, 0.81% comes from the investors. The foundation part, though unlocked, will still be held by us until further notice. So the effective unlock will only be 0.81%.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Based on the current price of $MASK, the 0.81% newly released tokens are worth $11,340,000 (assume $14 per $MASK), which is less than 20% of the daily trading volume of $MASK.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ll keep updating the latest information about the $MASK token release, please stay tuned for our official announcements!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/%7B%7B%20site.baseurl_root%20%7D%7D/uploads/771038253706819007.png" /></entry><entry xml:lang="en"><title type="html">Mask Network X Polygon｜Other ways to play?</title><link href="/2021/03/23/mask-network-x-polygon-other-ways-to-play" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mask Network X Polygon｜Other ways to play?" /><published>2021-03-23T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-03-23T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2021/03/23/mask-network-x-polygon-other-ways-to-play</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/03/23/mask-network-x-polygon-other-ways-to-play">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/699970589268454748.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mask Network will collaborate with Layer 2 solution aggregator Polygon (formerly Matic Network), to conduct technical conversations about the current issues, such as traffic and high gas fee on Ethereum, and to focus on performance optimization in the DeFi field, to create a faster and more practical decentralized environment for users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During Mask Network’s recent ITO of $MASK, we found that users have encountered unpleasant experiences, such as slow confirmation process and high gas fee. This has become not only a major issue for Ethereum, as the existing ecosystem cannot provide sufficient computation support, but also a challenge that open finance must overcome before it gets ready for the broader market.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Polygon proposed a solution: to simplify the interaction process between users and the decentralized world. In this collaboration, Mask Network will first integrate QuickSwap, a decentralized exchange that is part of Polygon’s ecosystem, enabling users to trade assets more quickly and with near-zero gas fee. We will then complete the integration with Polygon through joint bounty to further develop the ecosystem and explore new possibilities for operations such as payments and decentralized trading.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our first joint bounty:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://gitcoin.co/issue/DimensionDev/Maskbook/2645/100025307&quot;&gt;[Bounty] Integrate QuickSwap into Mask&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Polygon and Mask Network have reached a deep consensus on solving the current problems open finance is facing, and hope to work together to find ways to expand the capacity of Ethereum. Please follow @0xPolygon and @realmaskbook on Twitter for more information about the collaboration!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About QuickSwap&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;QuickSwap is a next-generation Layer 2 decentralized trading platform that enables lightning-fast transactions with near-zero gas fee. QuickSwap is based on Ethereum, with scalability infrastructure and funding provided by Matic on Layer 2, Quickswap looks to bring permissionless decentralized trading to Layer 2, replacing Uniswap and bringing the new era of decentralized finance to Layer 2.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Polygon (Formerly Matic Network)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Polygon is the first well-structured, easy-to-use platform for Ethereum scaling and infrastructure development. Its core component is Polygon SDK, a modular, flexible framework that supports building and connecting Secured Chains like Plasma, Optimistic Rollups, zkRollups, Validium etc and Standalone Chains like Matic POS, designed for flexibility and independence. Polygon’s Layer 2 Chains have seen widespread adoption with 100+ Dapps, ~12M txns and ~250K unique users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re an Ethereum Developer, you’re already a Polygon developer! Leverage Polygon’s fast and secure txns for your Dapp, get started&lt;a href=&quot;https://docs.matic.network/docs/develop/getting-started/&quot;&gt; here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://polygon.technology/&quot;&gt;Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/0xpolygon&quot;&gt; Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/maticnetwork/&quot;&gt; Reddit&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://t.me/maticnetwork&quot;&gt; Telegram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Mask Network&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mask Network creates a decentralized application ecosystem that bridges the gap between Web 2.0 (the existing Internet) and Web 3.0 (the new open Internet) for tens of thousands of users, helping them make a seamless transition. It provides the main function of encrypting and decrypting information transmission and evolves around this function, integrating de-private social, borderless payment network, decentralized file storage and sharing, decentralized finance, and governance (DAO) to help users protect their privacy, data, assets and rights on traditional social networks such as Twitter, Facebook, etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mask Network advocates that users should value their privacy, personal assets, and sovereignty, and firmly believes in an ownership economy. People should own their own creations, their own data, their own attention, and the virtual space they choose to contribute to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;table&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://mask.io/&quot;&gt;Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/realmaskbook&quot;&gt; Twitter&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/maticnetwork/&quot;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://discord.gg/4SVXvj7&quot;&gt;Discord&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://t.me/maskbook_group&quot;&gt; Telegram&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/%7B%7B%20site.baseurl_root%20%7D%7D/uploads/699970589268454748.png" /></entry><entry xml:lang="en"><title type="html">Mask Network invests in Convergence to join hands on Initial Twitter Offering (ITO) and Wrapped Security Token (WST)</title><link href="/2021/03/22/mask-network-invests-in-convergence-to-join-hands-on-initial-twitter-offering-ito-and-wrapped-security-token-wst" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mask Network invests in Convergence to join hands on Initial Twitter Offering (ITO) and Wrapped Security Token (WST)" /><published>2021-03-22T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-03-22T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2021/03/22/mask-network-invests-in-convergence-to-join-hands-on-initial-twitter-offering-ito-and-wrapped-security-token-wst</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/03/22/mask-network-invests-in-convergence-to-join-hands-on-initial-twitter-offering-ito-and-wrapped-security-token-wst">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/convergence.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mask Network has invested and partnered with decentralized interchangeable asset protocol Convergence to broaden the open financial system. Mask Network’s founder &amp;amp; CEO, Suji Yan, will be joining Convergence as an Advisor.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;As part of the partnership, projects on Convergence could conduct Wrapped Security Token launchings through Initial Twitter Offering provided by Mask Network and tradeable in the Convergence AMM pool.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mask Network and Convergence believe the partnership will bring greater market value and boost both platforms’ useability.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mask Network has recently announced investment and partnership with the decentralized interchangeable asset protocol Convergence. These two projects will work together to create a broader and more open financial system through infrastructure building, wrapped security token launching, and cross-product promoting.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mask Network has been dedicated to bringing DApps into traditional social platforms such as Twitter and Facebook to build a bridge between Web 2.0 and Web 3.0 for users. ITO (Initial Twitter Offering) stems from the foundation of IDO (Initial Decentralized Offering), the feature we launched recently is also based on such a vision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Convergence is a DeFi protocol that focuses on real-world assets, particularly in private unicorn companies. Firms could take advantage of the massive liquidity in the DeFi space by minting Wrapped Security Token (WSTs) through Convergence. This partnership means that various projects could conduct WSTs launching through ITO, and subsequently allowing users to trade within the AMM pool of Convergence.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Apart from that, these two projects hope to develop more fun and creative functions on the level of DApps. Both companies believe that launching WSTs through ITO is a way of connecting real-world assets to open finance. By collaborating with Convergence, Mask Network expects to develop more Twitter features, such as direct swaps/payments of WSTs through Twitter integrating with Convergence’s liquidity pools. This move could essentially bridge the real-world assets space and the Web 3.0 universe, making money more social and financial services more open as users could send and swap tokens via Twitter direct messaging.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This consensus of cooperation between Mask Network and Convergence will bring up greater market value and application value for both products. Besides the investment, Mask Network’s founder, Suji Yan, will be joining Convergence as an Advisor. With the help of technology support and ideas unity, we have faith in empowering a more open financial system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Oscar Yeung, Co-Founder of Convergence said, ‘We’re extremely excited to explore the synergies possible towards our mutual goal of enabling a more open, decentralized web where financial services are accessible to anyone.’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;- About Convergence&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Convergence will be the first AMM to make real world asset exposure interchangeable in the DeFi space by connecting Wrapped Security Tokens (WSTs) with Utility Tokens on a single interface that is easy to use, adopt and composable with other DeFi protocols.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Convergence enables asset owners to access decentralized DeFi liquidity, while DeFi users can access real world asset exposure (such as in private / unicorn companies or exotic real world assets). The vision of Convergence goes beyond this by integrating with other DeFi legos to further enable new and creative use cases.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;- About Mask Network&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mask Network is the core product of Dimension, which is positioned to become the bridge that connects internet users from Web 2.0 to Web 3.0. The foundational technology of Mask Network is a peer to peer encrypted messaging application, with new functions continuously being created around this foundation. We at Mask Network are strong believers in the ownership economy. People should own what they produce, people should own their data, their attention and the virtual space they choose to contribute to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mask Network integrates decentralized social messaging, borderless payment network, and decentralized file storage and sharing to provide a safe and convenient portal for users to jump right into the continent of decentralized finance and then the new world of Web 3.0.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/%7B%7B%20site.baseurl_root%20%7D%7D/uploads/convergence.png" /></entry><entry xml:lang="en"><title type="html">Mask Network Partners with NEAR Protocol, Raising a Joint Bounty to Kick it off</title><link href="/2021/03/16/mask-network-partners-with-near-protocol-raising-a-joint-bounty-to-kick-it-off" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Mask Network Partners with NEAR Protocol, Raising a Joint Bounty to Kick it off" /><published>2021-03-16T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-03-16T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2021/03/16/mask-network-partners-with-near-protocol-raising-a-joint-bounty-to-kick-it-off</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/03/16/mask-network-partners-with-near-protocol-raising-a-joint-bounty-to-kick-it-off">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/near.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are excited to announce that Mask Network has established a strategic partnership with the PoS blockchain NEAR Protocol. These two projects will cooperate between both of their base layer technologies as well as on the application front. The Rainbow Bridge, the NEAR EVM, NEAR Drop, and other key components are expected to be integrated when launched, in order to accelerate widespread adoption and engagement with NEAR Protocol and the Mask Network.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This cooperation will start with a joint bounty, allowing developers from communities to join forces and explore new opportunities at the intersection of these two projects. More specifically, the first bounty will be to facilitate &lt;strong&gt;the integration of the NEAR Wallet into Mask Network,&lt;/strong&gt; creating a solid foundation for future deployment of more NEAR based applications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The NEAR Wallet is NEAR Protocol’s non-custodial web wallet, using local storage on the users computer to store private keys in an open file format. This design is meant to provide more wallet options, and makes it easier to expand the NEAR developer community, while also marketing the determination of NEAR Protocol and the Mask Network to support one another in creating a vibrant decentralized web and finance ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The product idea of the Mask Network is a natural fit with the mission of NEAR Protocol. Both want to create a more free and open web, allowing users to control their own funds, data, and identity. This bounty is just the starting point of cooperation between the two projects. We have already planned a series of deeper integration projects and joint ventures that will be released to our communities over time. If you are interested in the Mask Network and NEAR Protocol, come join us!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The details of the Bounty can be checked in the link below:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://gitcoin.co/issue/DimensionDev/Maskbook/2602/100025151&quot; title=&quot;https://gitcoin.co/issue/DimensionDev/Maskbook/2602/100025151&quot;&gt;https://gitcoin.co/issue/DimensionDev/Maskbook/2602/100025151&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About NEAR Protocol&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NEAR exists to accelerate the world’s transition to open technologies by growing and enabling a community of developers and creators. NEAR is a decentralized application platform that secures high value assets like money and identity with the performance necessary to make them useful for everyday people, putting the power of Open Finance and the Open Web in their hands. NEAR’s unique account model allows developers to build secure apps that consumers can actually use similarly to today’s web apps, something which requires multiple second-layer add-ons on other blockchains.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Mask Network&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mask Network is the core product of Dimension, which is positioned to become the bridge that connects internet users from Web 2.0 to Web 3.0. The foundational technology of Mask Network is a peer to peer encrypted messaging application, with new functions continuously being created around this foundation. We at Mask Network are strong believers in the ownership economy. People should own what they produce, people should own their data, their attention and the virtual space they choose to contribute to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mask Network integrates decentralized social messaging, borderless payment network, and decentralized file storage and sharing to provide a safe and convenient portal for users to jump right into the continent of decentralized finance and then the new world of Web 3.0.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/%7B%7B%20site.baseurl_root%20%7D%7D/uploads/near.png" /></entry><entry xml:lang="en"><title type="html">DEGO x Mask Network | Build the NFT Entrance in Web 3.0</title><link href="/2021/03/10/dego-x-mask-network-build-the-nft-entrance-in-web-3.0" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="DEGO x Mask Network | Build the NFT Entrance in Web 3.0" /><published>2021-03-10T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-03-10T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2021/03/10/dego-x-mask-network-build-the-nft-entrance-in-web-3.0</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/03/10/dego-x-mask-network-build-the-nft-entrance-in-web-3.0">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/dego.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cross-chain NFT and DeFi protocol DEGO Finance has reached a strategic partnership with the Web 3.0 product Mask Network. Both parties will conduct further conversation on the development of NFT on traditional social media platforms, how to bring users more value, and build a NFT entrance in  Web 3.0 .&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DEGO Finance is a cross-chain NFT+DeFi protocol and infrastructure. Mask Network and DEGO Finance has reached an in-depth agreement in discovering how to land NFT’s functionality and finance characteristics. Through this cooperation, both parties will work together in fields such as NFT blind boxes, games, and social networks. Users will be able to conduct NFT creation, collection, buying and selling on Twitter, all with a few clicks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the bridge that connects Web 2.0 and Web 3.0, Mask Network also pays great attention to the NFT field. During the U.S. election in 2020, we have introduced “the Mask Network Election Special NFTs” and delivered 589 NFTs on Twitter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For more details on “Mask Network Election Special NFTs”, see below:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Introducing the Mask Network Election Special NFTs&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/22-1.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://news.mask.io/2020/11/04/introducing-the-mask-network-election-special-nfts&quot; title=&quot;https://news.mask.io/2020/11/04/introducing-the-mask-network-election-special-nfts&quot;&gt;https://news.mask.io/2020/11/04/introducing-the-mask-network-election-special-nfts&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Through the special NFT launch and the cooperation with DEGO Finance, we want to show that the transfer and display of NFT can be easily realized on centralized platforms such as Twitter. This is also why Mask Network exists, to keep integrating the boundaries between Web 2.0 and Web 3.0.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About DEGO Finance&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DEGO Finance is a cross-chain NFT+DeFi protocol &amp;amp; infrastructure, as well as an open NFT ecosystem where anyone can mint NFTs, initiate NFT mining, auctions and trading.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;DEGO Finance also offers a cross-chain infrastructure to enable Blockchain projects to grow their user base, distribute tokens, and to develop more diverse NFT-powered applications. DEGO Finance is building a Parachain through Substrate, enabling cross-chain NFT asset transfers, combining applications and underlying protocols.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Mask Network&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mask Network creates a decentralized application ecosystem, builds a bridge that connects Web 2.0(the existing internet) and Web 3.0(the new, open internet) for thousands of millions of users, so they could transition seamlessly. Its core function is information transmission encryption, with new functions continuously being created around this foundation. Mask Network integrates decentralized social messaging, borderless payment network, decentralized file storage, decentralized finance and DAO (Decentralized Autonomous Organization), to help users protect their privacy, data, assets, and rights on traditional social networks such as Twitter and Facebook. Mask Network advocates users to value and hold authority on their data privacy and personal assets. We at Mask Network are strong believers in the ownership economy. People should own what they produce, people should own their data, their attention and the virtual space they choose to contribute to.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/%7B%7B%20site.baseurl_root%20%7D%7D/uploads/dego.png" /></entry><entry xml:lang="en"><title type="html">$MASK is Officially on Fiat on-ramp Aggregator Transak, Now Supporting Direct Buying on Twitter</title><link href="/2021/03/05/mask-is-officially-on-fiat-on-ramp-aggregator-transak-now-supporting-direct-buying-on-twitter" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="$MASK is Officially on Fiat on-ramp Aggregator Transak, Now Supporting Direct Buying on Twitter" /><published>2021-03-05T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-03-05T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2021/03/05/mask-is-officially-on-fiat-on-ramp-aggregator-transak-now-supporting-direct-buying-on-twitter</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/03/05/mask-is-officially-on-fiat-on-ramp-aggregator-transak-now-supporting-direct-buying-on-twitter">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://assets.matters.news/embed/da78cd2c-5dc8-4d05-83b9-3ca5ce31904c.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mask Network has finished the public launch of the governance token &lt;strong&gt;$MASK&lt;/strong&gt; through &lt;strong&gt;ITO&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;LBP&lt;/strong&gt;, which raised significant attention from crypto-assets users around the globe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are thrilled to see buying enthusiasm the public has on the $MASK token. We hereby announce that the $MASK token is officially on &lt;strong&gt;Transak&lt;/strong&gt;, the fiat on-ramp aggregator endorsed by ConsenSys. &lt;strong&gt;Users can buy $MASK tokens directly using fiat money, without leaving Twitter.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Type “&lt;strong&gt;$MASK”&lt;/strong&gt; in the Twitter search bar, click “&lt;strong&gt;buy now&lt;/strong&gt;” and you are all set to purchase, no extra actions needed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://assets.matters.news/embed/655c46d0-535d-4814-899a-855fd5fde720.gif&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Under the technical support of Transak, now we are supporting legal fiat onramp channels from over 50 countries around the world, to purchase crypto-assets such as $BTC and $ETH directly on Twitter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, Mask Network will try to promote $MASK token towards the public sight, seeking collaborations with various decentralized projects, to further push the development of open finance, and build a bridge connecting Web 2.0 and Web 3.0.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;For details:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Introducing Transak — — The Fiat On-Ramp Aggregator on Mask Network&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://news.mask.io/2021/01/07/introducing-transak-the-fiat-on-ramp-aggregator-on-mask-network&quot; title=&quot;https://news.mask.io/2021/01/07/introducing-transak-the-fiat-on-ramp-aggregator-on-mask-network&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;https://news.mask.io/2021/01/07/introducing-transak-the-fiat-on-ramp-aggregator-on-mask-network&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Transak&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://assets.matters.news/embed/94b994a8-9118-4e94-80db-1f4e593a7bca.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Transak is a fiat on-ramp aggregator incubated by ConsenSys. Transak aggregates fiat onramp channels in more than 50 countries and supports multiple ways of payment including credit card, debit card and wire transfer. Transak is a partner with multiple world-renowned crypto projects including AAVE, Chainlink, Zilliqa, CryptoCompare and MetaMask.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;About Mask Network&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://assets.matters.news/embed/15e8e631-25a9-4416-854d-0a4888813aec.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mask Network creates a decentralized application ecosystem, helps tens of thousands of users to seamlessly transit from the existing Web 2.0 and the new, open internet, Web 3.0. Its core function is information transmission encryption, with new functions continuously being created around this foundation. Mask Network integrates decentralized social messaging, borderless payment network, decentralized file storage, decentralized finance and DAO (Decentralized Autonomous Organization), to help users protect their privacy, data, assets, and rights on traditional social networks such as Twitter and Facebook. Mask Network advocates users to value and hold authority on their data privacy and personal assets. We at Mask Network are strong believers in the ownership economy. People should own what they produce, people should own their data, their attention and the virtual space they choose to contribute to.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/%7B%7B%20site.baseurl_root%20%7D%7D/uploads/1-44.png" /></entry><entry xml:lang="en"><title type="html">$MASK Airdrop Round 1</title><link href="/2021/02/27/mask-airdrop-round-1" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="$MASK Airdrop Round 1" /><published>2021-02-27T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-02-27T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2021/02/27/mask-airdrop-round-1</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/02/27/mask-airdrop-round-1">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/2-33.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As of February 26th, 2021, $MASK initial public offering through ITO (Initial Twitter Offering) and LBP (Liquidity Bootstrapping Pool) has been a major success. We have been deeply touched by the support and enthusiasm of our community. You have walked with us through all the tribulations and airdrop is our way of saying thank you. Below is the detail of round one airdrop:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We have announced all the addresses that are eligible for round one airdrop and the respective amount and distribution of the airdrop in our previously published article “&lt;a href=&quot;https://news.mask.io/2021/02/17/introducing-the-mask-public-twitter-offering&quot;&gt;Introducing the $MASK Public Twitter Offering&lt;/a&gt;”. Meanwhile, users who have successfully purchased $MASK in ITO round 3 on February 24th, 2021 will also receive $MASK in airdrop round one. Originally we were airdropping 1.06 million $MASK to 15.9k addresses. Now with the success addresses from the ITO round 3, we are airdropping 1.86 million $MASK to 16.8k addresses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Airdrop details for the success addresses from the ITO round 3 are as followed:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If airdropped $MASK weren’t claimed in 24 hours, the claimable amount will be decreased by 20% of initial amount everyday.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Every address which has &lt;strong&gt;successfully purchased&lt;/strong&gt; 1111 $MASK will receive an &lt;strong&gt;airdrop&lt;/strong&gt; in the amount of &lt;strong&gt;889&lt;/strong&gt; $MASK.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If the purchase amount is less than 1111, then the airdrop will be &lt;strong&gt;proportional&lt;/strong&gt; to the amount they have purchased. For instance, if you had purchased 111 $MASK, then the airdrop would be 88.9 $MASK.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Locked $MASK token from round one airdrop and ITO campaign can be claimed starting 3:00am, UTC+0 on February 27th, 2021:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If airdropped $MASK weren’t claimed in 24 hours, the claimable amount will be &lt;strong&gt;decreased by 20%&lt;/strong&gt; of initial amount everyday until it reaches 0, which is to say, at the end of &lt;strong&gt;the fifth day&lt;/strong&gt;, the claimable amount will be 0.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;$MASK acquired during &lt;strong&gt;ITO&lt;/strong&gt; will always be available for claiming &lt;strong&gt;without any penalties&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;precautions&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Precautions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Please beware of the risk of the crowded service. Try to claim during low traffic time so as to reduce the chance of any convenience during the claiming process.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Make sure to NOT send fund to &lt;strong&gt;$MASK token contracts&lt;/strong&gt;. Mask Network team will not be responsible for any resulting losses.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Before claiming $MASK, make sure to bind your wallet to Mask Chrome Extension and have enough ETH as gas for a successful claiming.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Any addresses that have interacted with $MASK ITO contracts will be listed for round two airdrop. Stay tuned for more details about round two airdrop! (Keep track of official Twitter or Discord!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;claiming-your-mask-guide&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Claiming your $MASK guide:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bind your wallet that is eligible for airdrop with Mask Chrome Extension.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Click on the top left blue button that has “MASK” on it.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Click on “Claim” to claim your $MASK! (Ninjas won’t forget gas fees!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://assets.matters.news/embed/ed4710c5-b919-4b18-b9aa-6a6bea7747bf.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://assets.matters.news/embed/89ae93e8-1339-49d2-afa9-a3692c1870c0.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/%7B%7B%20site.baseurl_root%20%7D%7D/uploads/2-33.jpg" /></entry><entry xml:lang="en"><title type="html">$MASK LBP Tutorial</title><link href="/2021/02/24/mask-lbp-tutorial" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="$MASK LBP Tutorial" /><published>2021-02-24T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-02-24T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2021/02/24/mask-lbp-tutorial</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/02/24/mask-lbp-tutorial">&lt;h4 id=&quot;intro&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;INTRO&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The second part of the Mask public offering, the $MASK LBP will launch at 3:00pm UTC+0, Feb 24th and end at 3:00am UTC+0, Feb 26th, a total of 36 hours. We will use the Liquidity Bootstrapping Pool (LBP) by Balancer to auction 4% of the total supply in order to derive and capture the true value of $MASK.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;LBP (Liquidity Bootstrapping Pool) is a variant of dutch auction or reverse auction. Its price will drop if no one buys as time progresses. Please learn how it works before participating in LBP and stay within reasonable price ranges. Don‘t FOMO. Balancer changes the weight of its predetermined pool weight to push the price down if no participant is buying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;$MASK LBP Key Parameters&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the beginning of the LBP, we are going to put in 4,000,000 $MASK and $800,000 $USDC. The starting price is $3.9. Check out the table below for details:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/最后.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;key-links&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Links&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;$MASK Token Address：&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;0x69af81e73a73b40adf4f3d4223cd9b1ece623074&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Balancer:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://balancer.exchange/#/swap&quot;&gt;https://balancer.exchange/#/swap&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Reminder:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Due to the mechanism of reverse auction, the price will trend down automatically if no one buys. The declining slope is the steepest at the very beginning. &lt;strong&gt;Stay rational before any trade decisions.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-The default max slippage is &lt;strong&gt;0.5%&lt;/strong&gt;. Set it higher if you are buying with a relatively large order.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;how-to-participate-in-lbp&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to Participate in LBP&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to Purchase&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-After the LBP start at 3pm (GMT+0) Feb 24th, click &lt;a href=&quot;https://balancer.exchange/#/swap%E3%80%82&quot;&gt;https://balancer.exchange/#/swap&lt;/a&gt; and you will enter a page like the Picture 1 below.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Press connect on the top right corner, choose a wallet as shown in Picture 2.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/_20210224194010.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/8-13.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-After connecting your wallet, go back to the main page and select “Asset”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;$MASK LBP is paired with $USDC.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Please make sure that you have enough $ETH to pay for the gas in your wallet.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;If you choose other assets, Balancer will automatically convert to $USDC and then trade for $MASK. The additional step could cause the increase in the transaction fees.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/7-15.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/_20210224192908.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Type in the contract address of $MASK. &lt;strong&gt;0x69af81e73a73b40adf4f3d4223cd9b1ece623074&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Please make sure that you type in the correct address.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/5-21.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-Type in a reasonable amount at a reasonable price. Click “Swap”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/4-30.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All done. Have fun staying with your MASK！&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">INTRO</summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="" /></entry><entry xml:lang="en"><title type="html">Check Airdrop Feature is Live!</title><link href="/2021/02/22/check-airdrop-not-claimable-feature-is-live" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Check Airdrop Feature is Live!" /><published>2021-02-22T00:00:00+00:00</published><updated>2021-02-22T00:00:00+00:00</updated><id>/2021/02/22/check-airdrop-not-claimable-feature-is-live</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2021/02/22/check-airdrop-not-claimable-feature-is-live">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/1-43.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow our first round of $MASK ITO will commence. It’s time to release our airdrop recipient list. The check airdrop feature is live now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Install Mask if you haven’t already. Click the blue “MASK” button on the top left screen and you will be able to view how many $MASKs you are entitled to. It’s not claimable now though, you have to wait until Saturday, 3am (GMT+0) Feb 27th, 24 hours after our LBP sale concludes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tutorial on how to install Mask and check/claim airdrop&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://news.mask.io/2021/02/17/how-to-participate-in-ito-and-claim-airdrops-of-mask&quot; title=&quot;https://news.mask.io/2021/02/17/how-to-participate-in-ito-and-claim-airdrops-of-mask&quot;&gt;https://news.mask.io/2021/02/17/how-to-participate-in-ito-and-claim-airdrops-of-mask&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/2-43.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/3-43.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ve also put the entire recipient list on Arweave and IPFS. The link to the list is tweeted using Mask’s encryption technology. We welcome everyone to check it out.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Last time we said that: “Inspired by Uniswap, Badger and other DeFi and Web 3.0 projects, we will not only give rewards to $MASK to our early supporters. Ecosystem participants like Gitcoin donors and active voters in DeFi governance will also be rewarded to show our appreciation of their efforts. We hope this can promote more meaningful contributions to the ecosystem.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After running through the addresses a few times we are able to finalize the list. We‘d like to further demonstrate the rationale behind the scene as well as sharing a few interesting pieces of knowledge that we’ve found along the way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We divide the recipients into 2 major categories: Mask insider and Ecosystem Participants, and 6 sub categories as shown in the below table 1 and table 2.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Metrics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Total Number of Addresses Receiving the Airdrop: 15,949&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Total $MASK Airdropped: 1,067,780&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Median Amount: 50&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Average Amount: 67&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Number of Addresses Receiving &amp;gt; 200 $MASK: 147&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Number of Addresses Qualifying for &amp;gt;= 3 Sub-Categories: 62&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Table 1: Airdrop Classification and Number of Respective Recipients&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/4-31.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Table 2: Airdrop Amount Per Address by Classification&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/5-22.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mask Insider&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mask actually have a lot more features other than the 3 mentioned here. However we put user’s privacy as the utmost concern so we do not attempt any event tracking. Therefore we cannot obtain data from third party ethereum apps like Uniswap and 0x. We can only obtain addresses that have interacted with our own contracts, namely red packet, NFT and ITO. So here’s the airdrop for the participants of those 3 categories.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NFT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ve only issued NFT once, the election special. A total of 589 NFTs was given away free. We even covered gas back then. 230 holders for now, the guy with most NFTs has a whopping 66. 30 people have 5 NFTs or more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/6-20.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Red Packet&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Red packet was our first Ethereum based feature launched in Spring 2020. It pioneered in sending payment on top of Twitter in a decentralized manner. The Chinese New Year Red Packet campaign with Maker stormed the entire crypto Twitter. Ethereum founder Vitalik Buterin was even among the first batch of users and gave away some Ether for perhaps the only time since he is the famous “non-giver of Ether”. 110 addresses had more than 5 interactions with our red packet contract.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/7-17.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Initial Twitter Offering&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Initial Twitter Offering is our latest feature aimed to revolutionize the asset issuance market. We’ve successfully launched 2 offerings with Loopring and Mirror Protocol. 208 people participated in the 2 offerings. We are a bit surprised that 2 other offerings took place and 3 people participated. So we decide to give additional rewards to those 3 addresses. It is indeed permissionless so we welcome anyone to utilize the ITO feature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/uploads/8-13.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ecosystem Participants&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We thought long and hard about who should get the reward. Inspired by the list of eligible activities Badger, SDT and Float put forward, and some improvisation, we decided to reward 3 categories: governance voter, gitcoin donor and people who put their Twitter handle in a text record on ENS. These 3 represent 3 types of people who have contributed to the ecosystem growth and have well documented Ethereum addresses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Voters&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Voters include both Snapshot voters and voters of major projects that’s not in Snapshot: Maker, Compound, AAVE and Curve. We found a total of 11,828 addresses voted 2-10 times, and 1,575 addresses voted over 10 times. All dated before 1/1/2021.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A few interesting tidbits. In the 4 projects outside Snapshot, we found a total of 1,584 addresses voted 2-10 times, and 254 addresses voted over 10 times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Sushi has more than 3,000 voters, YFI 1,700+, Badger 1,300+, Maker and Yam 1,200+, Pickle 1,100+, AAVE 900+, Uniswap and Compound 600+.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gitcoin Donors:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We set the criteria to people who donated in more than 2 different rounds (out of 8 total) because a lot of people came in donating a minimal amount after the Badger airdrop. We found 1,253. We favor our own 275 donors a bit more, understandably.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ENS&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is our improvisation. We are first and foremost a project trying to bridge social networks and Web 3.0, so we look for people who tried a bit harder than others. We think putting Twitter handles on ENS text records is a very good indicator since this costs gas. We found more than 500 people. We didn’t do it other way around, i.e. putting ENS as twitter display name due to gameable concerns.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That concludes the explanation of our airdrop rationale. Have fun staying with your Mask!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary><media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="/%7B%7B%20site.baseurl_root%20%7D%7D/uploads/1-43.png" /></entry></feed>